[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以我也在重新考虑我放进去的东西
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So I'm also reconsidering things that I had put in in
那本书。
the book.
我当时还认为我说的话是好的吗？
Do I still think the things I said were good then?.
他们现在好吗？
Are they good now?
所以，在书中，我不推荐使用new。
So, in the book, I didn't recommend use of new.
我停止使用它，我建议使用Object.create，事实上，
I stopped using it, I recommended using Object.create instead, and in fact,
我设法将Object.create添加到语言中，这样我就可以使用它了。
I managed to get Object.create added to the language just so that I could use it.
所以，我真的很惊讶地注意到我已经停止使用
So, I was really surprised to kind of notice that I've stopped using
创建对象，这样做的原因是因为我停止了使用它。
Object.create, and the reason for that is because I stopped using this.
如果您不使用这个，那么create不会为您做那么多，而且
If you're not using this, then create doesn't do all that much for you, and
我停止使用这个的原因是因为Adsafe。
the reason I stopped using this was because of ADsafe.
因此，在2007年，有许多实验试图找出如何
So in 2007 there were a number of experiments at trying to figure out how to
将JavaScript转换为一种安全的语言来进行mashup和
turn JavaScript into a secure language for doing mashups and
在第三方交互中。
in third party interaction.
Facebook有FBJS，微软有网络沙箱。
There was FBJS at Facebook, there was web sandbox of Microsoft.
谷歌有Caja项目，还有我自己的Adsafe项目。
There was the Caja project at Google and there was my own ADsafe project.
每个人都在努力解决的难题之一是，
And one of the difficult problems everybody was struggling to solve was,
你怎么处理这件事？
what do you do about this?
因为如果你有办法
Because if you have a method,
这将绑定到感兴趣的对象，这很好。
this will get bound to the object of interest and that's good.
但如果调用与函数相同的方法，
But if you call that same method as a function,
这将绑定到全局对象，从而提供场。
this gets bound to the global object, which gives away the farm.
那你是怎么处理的？
And how do you deal with that?
所以其他三个项目采用的方法是，他们有翻译人员，
And so the approach that the other three projects took wa,s they have translators,
他们阅读JavaScript并编写JavaScript。
they read JavaScript and they write JavaScript.
而且他们写的JavaScript要大得多
And the JavaScript they write is much bigger,
因为他们添加了很多运行时检查和间接检查，以便找到
because they're adding a lot of runtime checking and indirection in order to find
在这种情况下，它会变成一个全局对象，并允许发生不好的事情。
cases where this is turning into a global object and allowing bad things to happen.
我对Adsafe采取的方法要简单得多。
The approach I took with ADsafe was much simpler.
我说，这是违法的。
I said, this is illegal.
所以如果我们看到一个包含这个的程序，我们就会拒绝它，完成，很容易。
So if we see a program with this in it, we reject it, done, easy.
所以我们不会重写程序。
So we don't rewrite the programs.
我们不会让它们更难调试或运行更慢。
We don't make them harder to debug or slower to run.
如果一个程序通过了Adsafe，它就可以全速运行而不需要任何修改。
If a program passes ADsafe, it gets to run at full speed without any modification.
但是Adsafe规则会拒绝
But the ADsafe rules would reject
相当接近Web上所有现有程序的100%。
pretty close to 100% of all existing programs in the Web.
因此，为了使用Adsafe，您必须使用Adsafe方言。
So in order to use ADsafe you had to work in the ADsafe dialect.
所以我决定做个实验，我会用那种方言工作。
So I decided as an experiment, well I'll work in that dialect.
我要看看是什么样子，有多痛苦。
I'll see what it's like and how painful it is.
现在，在与它合作了一段时间之后
Now after working with it for
有一段时间，我真的很惊讶地发现它变得更容易了。
a while I was really surprised to learn that it got easier.
我以为这会是一件艰难的事，我不得不四处走走，但是
That I expected it was gonna be a hardship that I was gonna have to get around, but
它实际上变得更容易了，我的程序也变得更好了。
that it actually got easier and my programs were getting better.
我被迫使用功能模式，因为原型模式
I was forced to use the functional patterns because prototypal patterns
没有，因为我停止使用这个，我真的很喜欢它。
weren't available because I stopped using this and I really liked it.
所以当我对这个模型有信心的时候
And so as I've gained confidence in this model and
我现在已经成为一个完全摆脱这个的倡导者，而且
I've become an advocate now of getting rid of this entirely, and
所有的都是函数，因为那才是好的地方。
going all with functions because that's where the goodness is.
是吗？&gt；&gt；演讲者2：JSLint说了什么
Yeah? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What does JSLint say about
这个？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那么JSLint，
this? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So JSLint,
这现在是一个选项。
this is now an option.
因此，现在有一个选项，您可以指定哪个选项将禁止警告
So there is now an option that you can specify which will suppress warnings
关于这个。
about this.
我不建议使用该选项，但它确实存在。
I don't recommend using that option but it's there.
我向JSLint添加了用于转换的选项，因为over
I added options to JSLint for a transition, because over
我一直在看的时间，我如何才能使这门语言变得更小更好？
time I'm constantly looking at, how can I make this language smaller and better?
去年我认为可能是个好主意的事情，
And things that I thought were maybe a good idea last year,
今年我想我不确定。
this year I'm thinking I'm not sure.
就像今年，我开始决定贴上“休息”标签可能不是个好主意，
Like this year I'm starting to decide that labeled break is probably a bad idea,
我已经很多年没用过了，我觉得我更适合
that I actually haven't used one in many years and I think I'm better for
很多年没用过了。
not having used one in many years.
因此标记的Break正在进入坏部件列表中。
So that labeled break is on its way onto the bad part list.
但是有些人使用JSLint，当JSLint规则改变时，就会去啊。
But there are people using JSLint who, when JSLint rules change, go aah.
我们习惯了这样做，现在不能这样做。
We're used to doing that and we can't do that now.
所以我增加了选项，这样他们就可以中转了。
So I add the options so that they can transit out.
我们现在只能勉强过关，最终我们会修复我们的代码。
We can just get by for now and eventually we'll fix our code.
除了发生的是人们不修复他们的代码和
Except what happens is people don't fix their code and
他们根据他们可以打开的选项来设计他们的编程风格。
they design their programming style based on what options they can turn on.
所以我现在尝试从JSLint中尽可能多地删除选项，
So I'm trying to remove options now from JSLint as much as I can,
但我最近添加了此选项
but I recently added the this option so
我们可以转机离开。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：您不使用原型
we can transit out. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You don't use prototypes at
所有的代码都是你自己写的？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我没有使用
all in the code you write, you personally? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I am not using
不再是原型了。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，所以Ben指出
prototypes anymore. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, so Ben pointed out
昨天，函数相对于对象的缺点之一是您的所有
yesterday that one of the drawbacks to function versus objects is that all your
函数，你拥有的每个函数，都有一个该函数的实例。
functions, every function you have, there's an instance of that function.
那是函数式编程-&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，
That's functional programming that's- &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah,
我们会讨论这个。
we're gonna talk about that.
接下来就是这个。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，
That's coming up next. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay,
我是想说放弃原型还有其他缺点吗？
I was gonna say are there any other drawbacks to abandoning prototypical?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：就是这个。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That's the one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以我停止了
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So I've stopped
使用NULL。
using null.
JavaScript有两个底值，至少比它应该多一个。
JavaScript has two bottom values, which is at least one more than it should.
所以我停止使用null，我只使用undefined now表示所有内容。
And so I'd stopped using null, I just use undefined now for everything.
即使打字时间更长，这也无关紧要。
Even though it's longer to type it, that doesn't matter.
所以，我不再依赖虚假。
So, and I stopped relying on falsiness.
我过去认为虚伪是个好主意
I used to think that falsiness was a good idea and
我主张进行尽可能小的比较和假设。
I advocated having comparisons and ifs that were as small as possible.
我现在认为这是一个错误，我们应该试着进行比较
I now think that was a mistake, that we should be trying to make comparisons that
尽可能明确，试图聪明地将真实情况分成两部分
are as explicit as possible, trying to intelligently bifurcate the true cases
从虚假案件中。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我已经停止使用
from the false cases. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I've stopped using
因为，因为在五年中我们得到了Foreach和Every以及MAP和
for, because in years five we got foreach and every and map and
所有那些人和那些人都很棒。
all those others and those are great.
所以在大多数情况下，我不需要再使用for loop了。
So for most purposes I don't need to use for loops anymore.
我不使用for in，因为我设法将object.key从ES5中取出。
I don't use for in, because I managed to get object.keys out of the ES5.
因此，in无论如何都不会正确工作，因为它总是会疏通
So for in never worked correctly anyway, because it would always dredge through
原型链和所有继承的方法都会出现，
the prototype chain and you get all the inherited methods coming up,
然后你必须过滤掉。
which you would then have to filter out.
因为从来没有正确的工作。
For in never worked right.
所以ES6将会有适当的尾部呼叫，当我们得到尾部呼叫时，
So ES6 will have proper tail calls, and when we get that,
我会停止使用while。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：So
I will stop using while. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So
下面是重复功能的两个版本。
here are two versions of the repeat function.
repeat接受一个函数作为参数，并且
repeat takes a function as an argument, and
我们将调用它，直到它返回undefined。
we'll call it until it returns undefined.
这是一个使用循环编写的版本，这是一个使用尾递归的版本。
And that's a version written using a loop, and that's a version using tail recursion.
在ES6中，
In ES6,
它们都应该以相同的速度运行，都需要消耗相同的内存量。
these should both run at the same speed, both consuming the same amount of memory.
因此这可能是ES6中实现的最后一个功能，
So this will probably be the last feature implemented in ES6,
所以我还在等它。
so I'm still waiting for it.
但是当它到来的时候，我完成了循环，我会
But when it comes, then I'm done with loops and I'm gonna
从现在开始做尾递归。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：在引擎盖下，
be doing tail recursion from here on out. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Under the hood,
为了防止出现这种情况，尾递归看起来像什么
what does tail recursion look like in order to prevent from having this
非常长的堆栈？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这真的很简单。
extremely long stack? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It's really simple.
只是这变成了跳转，它就像一个带有参数列表的goto。
Just this turns into jump to, it's like a goto with an argument list.
所以我们跳到重复函数。
So we jump to the repeat function.
所以我们要跳到顶端。
So we're jumping to the top.
如果这有一个新的值，而它没有，
And if this has a new value, which it doesn't,
新值将在这里被赋值，然后我们再来一次。
the new value would get assigned up here and we go again.